<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
  <!-- Update Mechanitor scenario to match 40k lore and add red robe/hood -->
  
  <!-- Update scenario label -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Mechanitor"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>The Tech-Priest</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>
  
  <!-- Update scenario description -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Mechanitor"]/description</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>You were an emissary of the Cult Mechanicus – tech-adept, magos biologis, or bond-servant of the Machine God – dispatched to a minor frontier world to reclaim lost archeotech and establish a foothold for the Adeptus Mechanicus. Your mission: locate and secure any remnants of ancient technology, establish a manufactorum, and spread the sacred knowledge of the Omnissiah to this backwater system.\n\nInstead, disaster struck. A miscalculated warp translation and a catastrophic reactor cascade tore through your vessel's hull, hurling you toward the surface in a coffin of scrap metal and screaming machine-spirits. The ship's cogitators screamed their death-songs in binharic cant as the void claimed your crew.\n\nYour escape pod survived the crash, along with a handful of sacred schematics encoded in data-slates and a small cohort of battered servo-skulls. Their machine-spirits are fractured, their housing damaged, but they still answer your signals through the sacred binharic protocols… for now.\n\nAlone on this backwater rock, far from the great forge worlds of Mars and Ryza, you will raise your own manufactorum from the dust. Strip the land, harvest ore, rebuild your steel servants, and black out the stars with the smoke of industry – all in honor of the Omnissiah. Through sacred rites and binharic protocols, you will forge new servo-skulls and servitors, establish a cybernetica control network, and perhaps one day contact the greater Mechanicus to report your findings.\n\nBut beware: this world is not empty. Ancient threats slumber beneath the surface, and the xenos are ever-present. Your faith in the Machine God and your mastery of cybernetica will be tested.\n\nNote: Since your starting character will lack some skills, this is a difficult scenario.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <!-- Update game start dialog -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Mechanitor"]/scenario/parts/li[@Class="ScenPart_GameStartDialog"]/text</xpath>
    <value>
      <text>You were an emissary of the Cult Mechanicus – tech-adept, magos biologis, or bond-servant of the Machine God – dispatched to a minor frontier world to reclaim lost archeotech and establish a foothold for the Adeptus Mechanicus.\n\nInstead, disaster struck. A miscalculated warp translation and a catastrophic reactor cascade tore through your vessel's hull, hurling you toward the surface in a coffin of scrap metal and screaming machine-spirits. The ship's cogitators screamed their death-songs in binharic cant as the void claimed your crew.\n\nYour escape pod survived the crash, along with a handful of sacred schematics encoded in data-slates and a small cohort of battered servo-skulls. Their machine-spirits are fractured, their housing damaged, but they still answer your signals through the sacred binharic protocols… for now.\n\nAlone on this backwater rock, far from the great forge worlds of Mars and Ryza, you will raise your own manufactorum from the dust. Strip the land, harvest ore, rebuild your steel servants, and black out the stars with the smoke of industry – all in honor of the Omnissiah.</text>
    </value>
  </Operation>
  
  <!-- Update scenario summary -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>Defs/ScenarioDef[defName="Mechanitor"]/scenario/summary</xpath>
    <value>
      <summary>One tech-priest and a few servo-skulls.</summary>
    </value>
  </Operation>
</Patch>

