<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>
  <!-- CREATURES -->
  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Militor"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Necron Warrior</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Militor"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A basic infantry construct of the dynasty, animated by ancient necrodermis and driven by a fragment of a long-dead consciousness. The Necron Warrior advances with mechanical precision, its gauss flayer disintegrating organic matter into molecular dust with each silent pulse. These are the foot soldiers of an empire that predates humanity itself, awakened from eons of slumber to reclaim what was once theirs.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Scyther"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Flayed One</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Scyther"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A deranged close-combat construct whose skeletal frame is draped in tattered scraps of flesh and metal. The Flayed One stalks forward in eerie silence before erupting into a frenzy of slashing blades, carving foes apart at terrifying speed.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Lancer"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Deathmark</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Lancer"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A precision execution construct, patiently stalking from extreme range. The Deathmark locks onto a target with unnatural focus before unleashing a single, devastating shot that can punch through armor and bone alike.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_CentipedeBlaster"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Heavy Destroyer</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_CentipedeBlaster"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A massive floating gun-platform bristling with ancient weaponry. Slow but relentless, the Heavy Destroyer saturates the battlefield with searing energy beams designed to tear apart fortifications, vehicles and clustered infantry.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Pikeman"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Immortal</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Pikeman"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>Elite line infantry of the dynasty, built on heavier frames and clad in reinforced alloy. Immortals advance with methodical, unhurried steps, laying down disciplined volleys of fire that grind resistance into dust.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Diabolus"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Doomsday Monolith</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Diabolus"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A towering, floating obelisk of obsidian metal inscribed with alien sigils. The Doomsday Monolith projects waves of annihilating energy, turning the battlefield into a killing ground where few living things survive for long.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Warqueen"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Canoptek Tomb Stalker</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Warqueen"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A predatory tunnel-hunter that slithers beneath the soil before erupting amidst its prey. The Canoptek Tomb Stalker coordinates lesser constructs as it tears through lines, shredding isolated targets with bladed limbs and segmented mandibles.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Apocriton"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Overlord</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Apocriton"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>The ruling will of the dynasty given form: a regal, heavily armored commander surrounded by crackling fields of energy. The Overlord directs allied constructs with ruthless efficiency, returning from apparent destruction again and again to complete its grim designs.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Termite_Breach"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Canoptek Spyder</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Termite_Breach"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A heavy support construct that crawls forward on multiple limbs, surrounded by swarms of smaller repair and cutting drones. The Canoptek Spyder specializes in tearing down walls and emplacements, opening breaches for other units to pour through.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Centurion"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Necron Pylon</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Centurion"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>An ultraheavy defensive construct that anchors the dynasty's battle lines. The Necron Pylon projects a powerful shield barrier that protects nearby units while its integrated point-defense turret tracks and eliminates threats with terrifying precision. This massive construct moves with ponderous inevitability, its ancient systems humming with the power of eons.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Cyclops"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Doomstalker</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Cyclops"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A towering sentinel construct dominated by a massive optical array that glows with baleful energy. The Doomstalker locks onto shielded targets with methodical precision, then unleashes a devastating barrage of shield-piercing beams that strip away defenses before annihilating the target beneath.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationReplace">
    <xpath>/Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Tesseron"]/label</xpath>
    <value>
      <label>Gauss Destroyer</label>
    </value>
  </Operation>

  <Operation Class="PatchOperationAdd">
    <xpath>Defs/PawnKindDef[defName="Mech_Tesseron"]</xpath>
    <value>
      <description>A mobile weapons platform armed with a devastating gauss beam array. The Gauss Destroyer sweeps its weapon across the battlefield, the searing energy beam capable of piercing even the thickest armor and igniting energy shields in cascading failures. While vulnerable to direct assault, its long-range firepower makes it a terror on the open field.</description>
    </value>
  </Operation>
</Patch>
